<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sundarcodes</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on sundarcodes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A-Z of JavaScript</title>
      <link>/post/a-z-of-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-z-of-javascript/</guid>
      <description>This is my collection of A-to-Z terms that one should knowing if they are into serious javascript programming.
Async/Await Async and Await are new features introduced in the language to make asynchronous code block look synchronous and more importantly make it more readable.
Brendan Eich Brendan Eich is the creator of JavaScript. He created the language in a matter of 10 days when working for Netscape Navigator. Due credit to be given to him for creating this language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front End development Analogy</title>
      <link>/post/front-end-analogies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/front-end-analogies/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we learn about some topics or if you are teaching someone, I always felt analogies from day to day life makes a greater impact to a person&amp;rsquo;s understanding. This post is my take on analogy of technologies/terminologies/people involved in front end development.
I am going to compare building a website to building a house where :
HTML(HyperText Markup Language) would be the raw building materials namely bricks, steels, cement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git workflow - my ramblings</title>
      <link>/post/git-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/git-workflow/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I would be talking about the git workflow that could be adopted when you are working on a project all alone and also when you are working in a team. Before we start, lets try to understand what is Git and why it is becoming the leader in Version control/SCM (Software Configuration Management).
What is Git ? Git is a version control system with a de-centralized approach to source control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Difference between AngularJS and Angular</title>
      <link>/post/angularjs-vs-angular/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/angularjs-vs-angular/</guid>
      <description>Angular the framework as this is what the Angular team would like to call, has evolved(and evolving) from being the most popular front end JavaScript framework over the last 5 years to a framework that has transformed itself to survive and be a leader for years to come. All references to Angular points to the version 2 and above and AngularJS means Angular 1.x.
In this post, we would be seeing how different is Angular and what are the new additions it is bringing to the world of Single Page App development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>